{
    "subject": "resource/Thomas_Burlison,_Baron_Burlison",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthYear",
    "object": "1936",
    "human_readable": "Thomas Burlison, Baron Burlison was born in 1936.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9752311706542969,
            "question": "When was Thomas Burlison, Baron Burlison born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9671319127082825,
            "question": "Is Thomas Burlison, Baron Burlison's birthdate in the 1900s?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9519327282905579,
            "question": "Was Thomas Burlison, Baron Burlison born before 1940?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9384854435920715,
            "question": "In which decade was Thomas Burlison, Baron Burlison born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9049486517906189,
            "question": "What is Thomas Burlison, Baron Burlison's birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8831329345703125,
            "question": "What was the historical context during Thomas Burlison, Baron Burlison's birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7903041839599609,
            "question": "Is Thomas Burlison, Baron Burlison a relatively recent historical figure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7472765445709229,
            "question": "What significant events might have happened in the world during Thomas Burlison, Baron Burlison's birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6629959940910339,
            "question": "How old would Thomas Burlison, Baron Burlison be today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6612679958343506,
            "question": "What year did Thomas Burlison, Baron Burlison come into this world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Thomas Burlison, Baron Burlison was born in 1936.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2464_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old would Thomas Burlison, Baron Burlison be today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2464_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What significant events might have happened in the world during Thomas Burlison, Baron Burlison's birth year?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2464_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Thomas Burlison, Baron Burlison a relatively recent historical figure?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2464_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2464_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2464_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2464_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2464_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2464_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2464_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2464_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2464_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2464_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2464_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to Thomas Burlison's birth year, including:\n\n* \"He began life as Thomas Burlison in 1936...\"\n* \"Thomas Henry Burlison was born on 23 May, 1936...\"\n* \"Born in Edmondsley, four miles north-west of Durham, Lord Burlison began his career as a panel beater and became a life peer in Tony Blair's first induction to the House of Lords in 1997. He was born in 1936.\"\n\nThese references confirm that Thomas Burlison, Baron Burlison was indeed born in 1936."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that \"He [Thomas Burlison] was born in Edmondsley, near Durham, of typical working-class stock, in 1936.\" and \"Thomas Henry Burlison was born on 23 May, 1936,\" which supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}